Your mom made you sit out in the sun again?
Then let me shade you.
Thank you, Sister Xiaowei.
What kind of
book is this?
It's a book
about women's pursuit of fairness and justice.
Let me share a quote with you.
At all times,
you must have courage,
whether it's to defend yourself,
or to defend a friend.
So right now, Sister Xiaowei
is defending me.
You bitch!
How dare you seduce my son!
Have you no shame in broad daylight!
I didn't.
Mom!
Don't touch Sister Xiaowei!
And you!
You're nothing but trouble too!
When someone seduces you,
can't you say no?
Mom, it has nothing to do with Dongdong.
Mom!
Did you think just because he's a cripple,
you'd be good enough for him?
And you could marry into the Cheng family?
How can you be so shameless?
I didn't.
You wish.
In your dreams!
Sister Xiaowei!
You bitch!
Are you okay, Dongdong?
Are you hurt?
It was her.
Sister Sang Luo pushed me into the water!
Mom.
As you know,
Dongdong never lies.
It was Sang Luo.
Sang Luo tried to kill him!
What is this?
You should be familiar with this, Aunt.
Isn't this just from when he
got bruised falling into the water?
This is a sunburn.
It's a mark left from you making him stay
out in the hot sun for four hours every day.
It's proof that you, as his mother,
to vent your frustrations,
have been abusing him.
How have you been taking care of Dongdong?!
I...
Grandmother.
Dongdong already has trouble with his legs.
So,
no matter how Aunt tortures him,
he can only obey.
Even if it hurts
or burns,
he still has to stay out in the sun,
not daring to move an inch.
Aunt abuses Dongdong like this every day.
Did you know about this, Grandmother?
E-
Even if he really does have sunburns,
that still
doesn't prove Sang Luo didn't push him!
Dongdong.
Tell the truth.
Did I push you into the water?
I...
Enough.
Dongdong has limited mobility.
It's normal for him to fall in accidentally.
As for this matter,
let's leave it at that.
Mom!
Shut up!
Mom...
You filthy sewer rat.
I'll definitely catch you next time.
You're right.
I am a sewer rat.
So, Aunt,
you'd better watch your back.
Don't let me catch you.
Otherwise, just like a rat,
I'll tear off your flesh, bite by bite.
By the way, Aunt.
Stop what you're doing to Dongdong.
The most pathetic thing about him
isn't his disabled body,
it's having a mother like you.
You...
Psycho!
I don't ever want to hear you say that again.
At the end of the day,
she's still my eldest brother's child.
I won't allow you to bully her like this.
My eldest brother is dead.
So as for you,
you don't have to follow him like a dog.
Sis,
Big brother was the only one kind to me.
If everyone plays nice,
we can all live in peace.
But if you insist on causing her trouble,
then I'll bite you to death.
You've lost it!
Are both of you out of your minds?
You two are just a pair of psychos, right?
You're all psychos! Just crazy!
What happened today...
nobody else saw it, but I did.
Dongdong falling into the water...
don't you feel the slightest bit of guilt?
Only people living well can afford guilt.
Why should I feel guilty?
Endure it.
I've endured more than enough in the past.
Now, I only swiftly dispose of
anything that has no further value.
And then what?
What are you going to do next?
Next,
I'm going to change my clothes.
Are you going to stay here, Little Uncle?
Look into Sang Luo's past for me.
I need every single detail.
As soon as possible.
Do it yourself.
Good morning, Aunt.
Eating so much protein?
Working out?
The doctor said
to eat more high-quality protein.
It's good for the baby.
Baby this, baby that.
Like you're the first one to have a baby.
Back in my day,
I didn't make such a fuss.
Aunt Lin is in great health.
She hasn't had morning sickness even once.
Actually, you don't need to eat this much.
I've had morning sickness too.
It's just that
it's not frequent.
You really are lucky.
Carrying a baby that doesn't cause trouble.
Unlike me.
Why aren't you eating?
I'm not hungry.
Then don't eat.
Don't ever eat again.
To earn money for medical bills.
She and her mother lived in the slums.
Her mom set up stalls, did cleaning,
and delivered food.
Since she was little,
she worked right alongside her.
As for her fingers...
it was after a cleaning shift
when she ran into a mugger.
Trying to protect her money,
they were brutally snapped.
Since she's part of the Cheng family,
her wanting to take back her share
is completely understandable.
But this Sang Luo gives me the feeling she's
hiding something.
What's in the water?
Nothing much.
Just some mulberry to trigger your allergy.
Ye Xiaowei.
I'm warning you.
Stay away from Dongdong.
Or next time,
it won't just be an allergic reaction.
The plan against Cheng Ruolin is moved up.
Also,
I'll be going to Gufeng Group next.
It'll be livelier than the Cheng family.
Cheng Ruolin caused you so much trouble,
yet you never considered changing the plan.
What happened now?
Suddenly changed your mind?
For a friend.
You ungrateful wretch!
You didn't help me when it mattered most,
you just kept your mouth shut!
That book Ye Xiaowei left you,
you treat it like a treasure.
Don't touch my book!
Don't look at me like that!
You look exactly like your useless father.
Do you know how he tortured me?
You owe me, your whole family owes me!
No...
No!
You cripple!
You damned cripple!
Stand up!
Do you hear me?!
Mom,
this is our company's new red wine.
I brought it especially for you.
Luoluo,
try this new product from the company.
I heard
the internal reviews are quite good.
Okay, Grandmother.
What's in this wine?
Grapes, of course.
But for a better taste,
we added some mulberries.
What?
Never had such good wine before?
This red wine
is rich and mellow,
with a playful hint of fruit juice.
Such a novel approach
is a first for me.
So I was a bit surprised.
Luoluo.
Take this wine back and enjoy it.
Taking care of me these past few days,
you've worked hard.
Okay, Grandmother.
Mom.
I brought this wine specifically for you.
I appreciate your filial piety.
Just say what's on your mind.
Grandmother,
Yes?
Aunt came specifically to see you.
She must have something to say.
I'll head back first.
Our Luoluo is so sensible.
Go on, go on.
Mhm.
Mom,
how could you, in front of Sang Luo,
say such things about me?
I am the most filial one.
I'm much better than that guy Cheng An.
Don't mention him in front of me.
And also,
if you're going to talk to me about money,
save your breath.
Mom,
don't be like this.
Can you please help me?
I just have a tiny deficit to cover.
If you don't help me,
no one else can.
You brought this upon yourself,
so go pay it off yourself.
Mom...
Mom!
This necklace is nice.
I happen to need one like this.
Just give it to me.
Thanks, Mom!
You ungrateful child!
What's wrong?
What happened to her?
Is she okay?
She drank some of my mulberry wine.
Maybe she had too much.
Cheng An,
have you been
doing well financially
lately?
You...
Sang Luo!
Open the door!
Are you okay?
Sang Luo!
What do you mean?
I'm trying to sleep.
Whatever it is, tell me tomorrow.
An allergic reaction is serious.
You could die!
Open the door!
If you don't open it, I'll break it down!
Take it.
Allergy medicine.
Who said I'm allergic?
I had a friend allergic to mulberry...
Since you're not allergic,
then go to bed early.
Where's the money and jewelry?
It was here a minute ago.
Where did it go?
I put away the jewelry and cards.
You come from a prestigious family.
If word gets out that you like to steal...
What do you mean by steal?
Everything you're wearing...
...was provided by the Cheng family.
And another thing.
You've known this Zhuang Sheng all along.
Right?
How do you have his files?
Put the files down.
You.
Get out.
It was you all along.
Why did you frame me?
If someone is stupid,
they should just lay low.
Then they can live in peace.
But look at you.
Not only are you stupid,
you also try to ruin others.
Zhuang Sheng
was a lesson for you and Auntie Ying.
Just bait to make you two dogs fight.
You scullery maid!
Did you think you could still
bully me like before?
What you just said,
I've already recorded it.
Director Cheng of Gufeng Group,
former Xie Group chairman's trophy wife,
loves being a thief.
If this gets out...
Lin Wanmei!
Don't think just because you're pregnant
you can strut around in the Cheng family.
I'm telling you,
I won't let you off!
No way.
Why not?
I need this money right now.
Director Cheng,
the funds diverted last time aren't back.
Right now,
if I move these funds out,
I'll use it for a month,
and the deficit will be covered.
Why can't I get this through to you?
Director Cheng,
it's not that I don't trust you,
but you say this every time.
And as a result...
Our deficit just keeps getting bigger!
Zhao,
you've been with the company for so long.
I've treated you well, haven't I?
So, are you on my side?
Of course I am.
It's just a small favor.
Are you going to help me or not?
I really can't this time.
If you're really in urgent need of money,
why don't you
ask Cheng An for help?
He definitely has the means.
Is he the boss, or am I?
Get lost!
Get the hell out of here!
Useless trash!
Accountant Zhao.
What are you doing here?
I...
was just reporting on my work.
Come on.
Have afternoon tea with me.
Good afternoon, Little Uncle.
What a coincidence.
Making some money?
Yeah.
Since I can't join and get paid,
can't I make a little money on my own?
If you want to work,
I can recommend you to other companies.
But I only want to join Gufeng Group.
Gufeng Group has the people I want to see.
Little Uncle,
you're so nice.
Why don't you help me out?
You're asking for too much.
I can't do that.
I'll find my own way then, Little Uncle.
I still need to warn you.
Gufeng Group isn't a clean place.
If you want a job,
you can totally find one you like more,
an easier job.
Are you done?
Then thank you, Little Uncle.
But as for me,
I'm not exactly a clean person either.
I just like diving into the trash.
Or I wouldn't be in the Cheng family.
Don't you agree?
I oppose Sang Luo joining Gufeng Group.
Sit down.
I'm still here.
Is it your turn to speak?
Grandmother.
Aunt probably thinks I'm too young,
and worries I won't be able to handle it.
But rest assured, Grandmother.
I'll definitely do my best.
Cut the innocent act.
Can just anyone join Gufeng Group?
Look at yourself and see if you're worthy.
Aunt Lin.
Our status in this house
is the exact same.
We're both isolated, helpless outsiders.
I agree Sang Luo can join Gufeng Group.
Lin Wanmei!
Have you lost your mind?
Her joining Gufeng Group...
what good does it do you?
We're all family.
Why talk about benefits?
Sang Luo is Brother Feng's child.
We should all lend her a hand.
Enough.
You, as her Aunt,
are worse than an outsider
at treating our own family well.
She
is your own niece.
I make the decision.
Let Luo Luo
work at Gufeng Group.
As for which department,
just go to Ruolin's department.
That way, Sang Luo
can show her Aunt what she's capable of.
Okay.
I'll go to Aunt's department then.
I'll make sure to impress Aunt.
Lin Wanmei.
Who knew the sophisticated President Lin...
is actually a scullery maid at home?
Why don't you use that thing in your belly
to throw your weight around anymore?
Have you heard this story?
If someone lives on the edge of a knife,
and one day they stop obeying,
you have to find a knife
to intimidate them once again.
Now I just want to know
if Ye Xiaowei
is still a useful knife.
From your expression, I can tell
this knife is still quite handy.
Don't forget,
in what happened to Ye Xiaowei,
you played a part too.
You've been in our family for so long.
How do you still not know your place?
If this gets out,
my mom will naturally protect me.
But what about you?
After you give birth to this child,
you'll be kicked out of the house.
Lin Wanmei,
I'm done wasting my breath on you.
Give me another million.
Didn't I just give you a million?
I don't have it.
That's your problem.
You need to remember,
as long as you're in the Cheng family,
and I have leverage over you,
you must always
respect me,
fear me,
and please me.
Oh,
right.
I wouldn't mind letting the company see
just how sophisticated President Lin truly is.
Why get so angry, Auntie?
As for partners,
picking a stupid one
is just asking for trouble.
A partnership
isn't about whether they're stupid,
but whether they're useful.
I am naturally more useful than Cheng Ruolin.
I won't do stupid things to annoy you, Auntie.
Speaking of which,
Aunt is quite pitiful.
A love-starved woman like her...
tell me,
if there were a man
who could give her some warmth,
would she still have the extra energy
to provoke you, Auntie?
After all,
to deal with a woman like Aunt,
a man is the best tool.
Then what do you want?
What I want doesn't matter.
What matters is keeping you happy, Auntie.
Mr. Cheng's car.
Who's that?
Yeah.
Getting out of Mr. Cheng's car.
Thanks for dropping me off, Little Uncle.
Ms. Lin is here.
Ms. Lin. Ms. Lin.
Let me introduce you all.
This is our new employee,
Sang Luo.
Hello, everyone.
My name is Ye Xiaowei.
I'm very happy that starting today,
I can be colleagues with you all.
In the future, if you have any
dirty or tiring work,
or need packages picked up,
you can leave it all to me.
It's been three years.
I'm back.
Hello, everyone.
My name is Sang Luo.
It's nice to meet you.
I look forward to working with you.
Then take a look around to get familiar.
I'll get back to work first.
Okay.
Xiaoxiao,
show her around.
Let's go.
Take a look here.
Okay, this looks about right.
Your outfit is so pretty.
This morning,
Mr. An dropped you off, didn't he?
The whole company is talking about it.
Why?
Are you two really close?
Do you think I should tell the boss
to move this Ye Xiaowei somewhere else?
I find her so annoying.
Just look at her outfit today.
Her sweater is pilling.
It's a disaster.
They're insulting you,
and you aren't saying anything?
Are you mute?
Mr. An is my Little Uncle.
So naturally, he'd drop me off.
As for this outfit...
it's authentic.
Of course it looks good.
Unlike yours.
It's a knockoff, isn't it?
What's so great about the Cheng family?
Nothing particularly great.
But you can't afford to mess with them.
She's also part of the Cheng family.
And she's your older brother's daughter.
Shouldn't you be happy I let her join the company?
Because I don't believe you'd be that kind.
Tell me.
What benefits did she give you?
So Mr. An
doesn't trust his own little niece.
Sang Luo's origins are a bit fishy.
I doubt Ms. Lin hasn't suspected anything.
If she is my older brother's daughter,
I will definitely protect her
and keep her out of Gufeng Group's mess.
But if she isn't,
I will naturally protect Gufeng Group too,
and stop external factors from ruining it.
Then, Mr. An,
which outcome are you hoping for?
What outcome I hope for doesn't matter.
But you, on the other hand...
taking such good care of someone
who will fight your baby for the fortune.
I find that very strange.
What's so strange about it?
Your older brother is gone.
As his wife,
shouldn't I care for his child for him?
Playing the good wife and mother now?
Others might not know your true colors,
but do you think I don't?
Mr. An, I think I need to remind you.
Sang Luo has finished her onboarding.
She's now a formal employee of the group.
If you want her to leave,
your only option is to fire her.
And to fire her, you'd need a valid reason.
Otherwise,
it'll be hard to explain to the old lady.
What's wrong?
Director Cheng.
Go to the storage room,
and get all the purchasing records
from the past three years sorted out.
What's so funny,
Miss Sang Luo?
Using your status in the Cheng family
to avoid doing normal work?
Lead the way, Director Cheng.
Where is the storage room?
You really are stupid.
Sort all these out for me.
Give them to me before you clock out.
Yes, Director Cheng.
Director Cheng,
this bidding document you just gave me...
I don't quite understand it.
What does this mean?
Sang Luo!
Open the door!
Open the door right now!
How can you be so vicious?!
How else could I work with you if I wasn't?
Enjoy your stay in there.
I figure it'll be a while
before I find anyone to rescue you.
If you get hungry,
just read the files.
Consider it food for thought.
Is this syrup really priced this high?
If I bring this price down,
wouldn't that cover the shortfall?
Let's go across the street.
Let's go, let's go.
All right.
Want to grab a bite together?
No, I'm good.
You guys go ahead.
Oh, okay.
How is it?
The food at Gufeng Group,
is it not as good as you imagined?
I just got here.
Whether the food is good
or bad,
I still have to eat it.
There was a girl once
who sat in this exact seat,
saying the exact same things as you.
But listen to me carefully.
Your petty tricks at home didn't matter.
Now that you're in the Group,
if you still dare to make waves,
I won't let you off.